trafficexplorer.com 2006-06-17

# Privacy Policy

|  Privacy Policy

We believe that people should be able to use the Internet without worrying about the unauthorised or unwarranted collection of their personal information. We disapprove of Spyware. Our Privacy Policy is spelled out in detail below.

1.      We do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information you provide when using the TrafficExplorer.com website.

2.      We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you (such as your name or email address) when you use TrafficExplorer.com unless you specifically decide to provide such information in order to enhance your TrafficExplorer.com experience. 

3.      If you choose to provide us with an email address, we will not send an email to you unless you specifically request an email response to a customer service inquiry or contact is required in order to protect someone's safety or to enforce our Terms of Service. You are not required to provide an email address to personalize TrafficExplorer.com. 

4.      When you visit TrafficExplorer.com, we may place cookies on your computer that allows us to identify your Web browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, and store your preferences and settings. Importantly, a cookie does not allow us to obtain any personally identifiable information (such as your real name and address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using TrafficExplorer.com. 

5.      If TrafficExplorer.com is ever sold or all or substantially all of the assets relating to the TrafficExplorer.com website and software are transferred to another entity, we will transfer the information you have provided (such as any stored preferences or toolbar settings) to the acquiring entity in order to ensure continuity of your personalized service. 

6.      We recognize and welcome our obligation to comply with the law and this policy is subject to that obligation. We will, therefore, disclose information, including cookies, in response to a request from law enforcement officials or as otherwise required by law, or if we believe it is necessary to protect someone's safety, or enforce our Terms of Service. If we decide to materially change this privacy policy, we will prominently post those changes on this page.

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us at [privacy@trafficexplorer.com](mailto:privacy@trafficexplorer.com).
